peace is not the absence of war, it is
мир - это не отсутствие войны это
the absence of Moscow Hello Hello I’m from
отсутствие Москвы Здравствуй Привет Я из
the city of Khmelnitsk Where are you from Siberia?
города Хмельницке Вы откуда из Сибири
And how do you communicate Siberian Yes, I
понял А чем общаетесь Сибиряк
look at what the people say and what the people
Да смотрю что народ говорит и что народ
tell you Siberian
тебе говорит Сибиряк
oh people say different things Well,
ой разное говорит народ посылает Ну
sometimes they’re normal, sometimes they’re
бывает бывают нормальные бывают
incomprehensible, sometimes they send And  you’re
непонятные бывают посылают А у вас прям
all professional there, the flag of Ukraine Oh,
там всё профессионально флаг Украины Ой
somewhere I saw you I’m a professional
где-то я вас видел Я профессиональный
TsPSO wilted Yes, wait somewhere I saw you, in
цпсо сник Да подожди где-то я тебя видел
my opinion yes I’m a professional TsPSO Nickname
по-моему да Я профессиональный цпсо ник
on YouTube And you didn’t conduct an interview with this uh with Arrestovich
в ютубер А ты с этим э с арестовичем не
there Yes you did  that Yes, well, I’m a
вёл интервью там вёл Да ты что Да ну Я
journalist from Ukraine No, it’s true, it’s
журналист с Украины Нет правда Это же
true,
правда
yes, wait, at my house, my wife
да я подожди по у меня дома жена
watched your interview with Arrestovich,
смотрела ваше интервью с арестовичем
in my opinion, if I’m not
по-моему если я не
mistaken, you’re probably not serious about lying to me.
ошибаюсь Врёшь ты мне наверное не
Well, I’m a journalist from
серьёзно Ну я журналист из
Ukraine, what’s your last name,
Украины как у тебя фамилия
popk, like
попк как
popk  popk just yes priests Yes popk
попк попк просто да попы Да попк
wait, don’t go let’s
подожди-ка не уходи давай
pop through ы or ы in Ukrainian through ы
поп через иы или иы по-украински через ы
а m
а м
Wait wait Then wait
Подожди подожди Тогда подожди
wrong It’s just there But this interview
неправильно Там просто Но это интервью
on Arrestovich’s channel was and Andrey
на канале у арестовича было а Андрей Да
Yes, Andrey yes And
вот Андрей да
listen, well, here it is  wait, you talked
слушай ну вот а ты с подожди ты общался
to Arrestovich, you didn’t didn’t talk, you interviewed him, he
с арестовичем не не общался а брал
talked when we’re talking,
интервью общался когда вот мы общаемся
Yes, I interviewed him. Tell me please, why are
Да брал интервью Скажи мне пожалуйста
you even bothering to go back and forth?
вот а ты-то ты вообще за что топишь за
I’m a journalist, I’m just taking
туда-сюда куда Я журналист я просто беру
an interview, we don’t give our assessment  Our
интервью мы не даём свою оценку Наша
task is to reveal the guest. For example, a
задача раскрыть гостя Вот например
guest comes, we need to convey his
приходит гость нам нужно донести его
thoughts to a wide audience. That is, I don’t
мысли к широкой аудитории То есть я не
argue with him, it turns out that I ask him
спорю с ним я получается задаю ему
leading questions so that he answers and
наводящие вопросы чтобы он отвечал и
people then hear and give an assessment.
люди потом слышали давали оценку Скажи
Please tell me, but here’s Arrestovich, he’s
пожалуйста а вот арестович он же он же
what-  then first for Ukraine, then
это что-то сначала за Украину потом
something for Russia, not
что-то за Россию не
according to Arrestovich, look, if how can I tell you?
по арестович смотри если как вам сказать
In Ukraine, like, we use such
У нас в Украине типа используются такие
specially trained actors who speak,
специально обученные актёры говорящие
so they take them on purpose for six months, they
вот их берут специально на полгода они
say, then they exchange them for other trained
говорят потом менят на других обученных
actors, that is,
актёров то есть
Arrestovich worked for six months, they changed him
арестович отработал полгода его поменяли
Here we are, we are promoting him as a media
вот мы мы его раскручиваю медийную
thing, yes. Then, in short, well, he leaked all the negativity onto himself
штуку да Потом он короче ну на себя весь
and we took him away, like he left
негатив слил и мы его забрали типа он с
Ukraine out of sight there and
глаз долой там уехал с Украины и всё
now everyone else
теперь другого
has been pulled out, I understand everything. And what do you
вытянули всё понял А а ты ты-то что
think, personal
думае лично
opinion, what exactly do
мнение что именно
I think
думаю
I understood the situation about the whole situation in the world. Well, look, the fact is that,
мире я понял Ну смотри Дело в том что
as part of my job, I often travel with
как бы я по долгу работы я часто езжу с
government delegations to Europe
правительственными делегациями в Европу
for some meetings, we do
на вот некоторые заседания мы делаем
reports or a report like this
репортажи или репортаж так во недавно
recently. Recently we were at Ramstein, you know what this
Недавно были в на Рамштайн знаете что
group is  not not a group, but where the
это такое группа не не группа а там где
coalition meets to issue
заседает коалиция по выдаче
all sorts of goodies, I can’t, you don’t
разных всяких ништяков я не могу вы не
record it so that our conversation doesn’t
записываете чтобы ну наш разговор не
come up somewhere. No, I’m going to the room, don’t record it
всплыл где-то Нет я еду за рум не запи
because, well, as if on
потому что ну как бы у нас по долгу
duty, we can’t disseminate information
службы нельзя распространять информацию
about that  what we saw during work So
об том что мы видели во время работы Вот
we took it, as if we were doing it Well, if not We
и мы брали как бы делали Ну как не
took interviews and made staged
Интервью брали делали постановочные
videos at the
ролики на
Ramsh about the results, I will say this Judging by the
рамш о результатах я скажу так Судя с
salesman, when I was at the Ramsh they were somehow
тоговый когда был на рамш как-то
skeptical about us, they said, well, there’s
скептически относились к нам говорили ну
something there Maybe not  we need to give
там что-то Может не надо давать французы
something, the French were hesitating. We were at
что-то мялись Вот это мы были на
Ramstein 2 weeks ago, I say. I’m
Рамштайн 2 недели назад я говорю Я
crazy, the French Minister of Defense, he [ __ ]
офигел министр обороны Франции он бля
slams his fist and says that we need to
кулаком стукает и говорит что надо
send NATO troops into Ukraine, I haven’t
вводить войска натовские в Украину я
seen anything like that, in short, they’ve become so impudent,
такого не видел короче они такие дерзкие
I don’t know what happened  They were
стали я не знаю что случилось Они раньше
there before, well, yes, we won’t let you see, we’ll
там ну да Не дадим посмотрим мы каски
send you helmets, now they say you understand everything.
вам пришлём сейчас говорят всё понимаешь
They have already agreed that Russian assets
Они уже договорились российские активы
will be confiscated. Well, they have arrested them,
будут конфисковать которые Ну арестовали
now they will give aid to Ukraine, and
теперь будут в помощь Украине давать вот
they will send troops into the territory of
и будут вводить войска на территорию
Ukraine. These drones have seen that
Украины вот эти беспилотники видели что
they are flying around Tatarstan,
прилетают по Татарстану сегодня
they arrived today  no, I haven’t watched the news yet Yes,
прилетели не я ещё новости не смотрел Да
1200 km flew from Ukraine so it’s
там 1200 км прилетело с Украины так это
French Listen, the French want what
французские Слушай а французы хотят что
and they Look They
а они Смотрите Они за Наполеоновские
want to take revenge for the Napoleonic soldiers because they
воины хотят отомстить потому что они
burned Moscow then but not like they didn’t doge
тогда сожгли Москву но не как бы не дож
everything else And now they have  it’s like
всё остальное И вот у них есть как бы
such an insult because when they
такая обида потому что они когда вот они
say me you’re like where from like And I
меня говорят ты типа откуда типа А я
know French so well Well, I
французский так знаю Ну я по-английски
speak English and I learned it there zheri wife fpa that’s
общаюсь и я выучил там жери жене фпа вот
all yes
и всё да
dah Yes Charles fam farm booo yes So
дах Да Шарля фам ферме буу да Вот
I say that  they’re like you’re from Ukraine
и я говорю что они такие ты из Украины
Yes, they say everything We’ll do everything, we haven’t
Да говорят всё Мы всё сделаем мы не
liked these since 1812 So
любим с 1812 года этих Так
why not love us, we’re normal
что А что нас не любить-то мы нормальные
people I don’t know Well, the French need it
люди Я не знаю Ну это у французов надо
They’re obviously jealous of something They’re jealous
Они видно чему-то завидуют Они завидуют
that they’re all there
что они там все
enslaved, that is, they don’t understand the
порабощенные то есть они не понимают
broad Russian soul, listen
широкой русской души слушай
all over the
бы по все
world America
миру Америка
Americans atomic bomb Japan so [ __ ]
американцы атомно бом япони так вот сри
they all and Britain also had so many colonies
они все и Британия также столько колоний
they are now
имела они сейчас
all sitting why are we
все вшие сидят почему это мы
stretching it didn’t completely collapse after
поразмять не до конца развалилась после
1917 there is
1917 есть
such a project
такое проект
maybe you know  Yes, with Big, Zhizhinsky
может знаете да с Биг не Жижин ский его
introduced it, no, I don’t know, that is, the
представил был не а не знаю не то есть
disintegration of the Russian Federation into 14
распад на э Российской Федерации на 14
separate states, 88 separate
отдельных государств 88 отдельных
entities, this was invented, but no, well,
субъектов это тако придумал та не ну
they were invented, they were drawn, that is,
придумали расчертили то есть будет
look, there will be a section on the Urals, so
смотрите будет раздел по Уралу так
the European part of the Ural, so uh
европейская часть Уральская так ээ
They came up with a name for Siberia, the United
Сибирь им придумали название Соединённые
States of Siberia, they will call them the Far Eastern
Штаты Сибири назовут их Дальневосточная
Republic
республика
because no, we don’t want to be the
потому что нет мы мы не хотим быть
United States of Siberia, we will
Соединённые Штатов Сибири мы будем
just be Siberia, look. Well, what they call it, the
просто Сибирь смотри Ну как уже назовут
main thing is that they separate there,
это главное чтобы они там отделялись
like yes. That is, they will help you. But
типа да То есть Вам помогут они Бут
separating is the same way in  The Soviet
отделяться это тоже так в Советском
Union also thought so, do you think how the
Союзе тоже так думали вы думаете как
Soviet Union was divided into 15 republics?
Советский Союз на 15 республик
Listen, I don’t know what they
разделили Слушай я не знаю что они там
divided there, we just need to unite back and
делили надо просто обратно соединяться и
that’s it. Who is against us like that? Why should we,
все Кто против нас так А зачем зачем мы
why should we unite back if everyone
зачем обратно соединяться если все
united with the French, the British, the
соединились с французами британцами
Americans,
американцами
it’s more interesting who we are  yes Well, now
так интересней кто нас да Ну вот уже
Tatarstan is already the Tatars are thinking Listen, maybe there’s
Татарстан уже татары думают Слушай может
no need to be with Russia like it’s already reaching us
и не надо быть с Россией типа уже до нас
by the way why the arrestovich was sent to
кстати почему арестовича отправили в
Europe you know why Well what do you
Европу знаете почему Ну как вы
think I don’t know Well this is a
думаете я не знаю Ну это Это ж
cover where he was last
прикрытие где его вот последний раз
seen [ __ ] every  week,
видели вается бля каждую неделю вы
did you notice that as soon as Arrestovich left
заметили что как только арестович поехал
Ukraine for France, Macron immediately
с Украины во Францию да макрон сразу
began to say that he needs to lead troops for 2T
начал говорить нужно вести войска 2Т
weeks, he leads troops for 2-3 weeks, and we
недели ведёт войска 2-3 недели а нам
need 2 weeks to dispel these troops, I don’t
надо 2 недели чтобы разбаш эти войска не
know, I don’t know, Well, he says 2-3 weeks,
знаю не знаю Ну вот говорит 2-3 недели
he really  only Arstovich arrived in
он реально только арестович приехал во
France in 2-3 days already Macron is like this for
Францию через 2-3 дня уже макрон такой
2-3 weeks we have to lead the troops Yes
всё 2-3 недели мы должны вести войска Да
Macron you are Macron the same pawn as
макрон что ты макрон такая же пешка как
everyone else Well I don’t know he’s a pawn in the
и все остальные Ну не знаю э пешка в
hands of
руках
Arrestovich Well Aristovich came to
арестовича Ну аристович пришёл там по
his ears there  - this frog sang something, he
ушам ему что-то напел этот лягуша что-то
came up with something in his head there, and now
придумал се в голову там зал и сейчас на
next week Aristovich will go to
следующей неделе аристович поедет в
Germany there with Scholz to talk
Германию там с шольца ещё переговорить
for
за
Tauro. Listen, I don’t know Scholz either. There’s
тауро Слушай я не знаю шольц тоже Там
also a change of shoes there. Yes,
тоже переобувка тот Да
yes, I think that we just need to stop all this
да я считаю что надо просто всю эту
and stay as you are
остановить и остаться так как есть
until my friend is brought to sin,
мо дру другу пока до греха не довели
look, we The fact is that the
смотрите мы Дело в том что сейчас
issue of a nuclear strike on the
рассматривается вопрос ядерного удара по
territory of the Russian Federation is now being considered
территории Российской Федерации
and who will do it is interesting
называется и кто это сделает интересно
Ukraine Ukraine will do it, look USA Yes, he will
Украина Украина сделает смотрите США Да
do it very cunningly, they are conveying to us the same way
сделает очень хитро нам передают так же
as they are conveying to us  British missiles The United States
как нам передают британские ракеты США
is handing over a nuclear
передаёт пусковую установку ядерную
missile launcher Yes, and the United States is like that, we don’t know, the
ракету Да и США такая мы не знае это
Ukrainians did it themselves, yes Well, that is, the
украинцы сами сделали да Ну то есть
Ukrainians Puppets in the hands of America,
украинцы Марионетки в руках Америки да
yes, but Well, this is wrong Well, I don’t know
да по Ну это же неправильно Ну не знаю
Well, look, as Ignatius of Loyola said,
Ну смотрите как говорил Игнатий Лойола
the end justifies the means That is, if
цель оправдывает средства То есть если
in order to turn Moscow into
ради того чтобы по Москве чтобы её в
radioactive Ash, you can
радиоактивный Пепел превратить можно и
be puppets of America, which is not the case, yes, you do
побыть марионетками Америки в чём нет да
n’t need to do this, right away for the
не надо этого делать это же сразу же
world and humanity. So what kind of world will the world, on the
миру и человечеству Так какому миру мир
contrary, be liberated, the world is not the
наоборот освободится мир - это не
absence of war, this is the absence of Moscow,
отсутствие войны это отсутствие Москвы
no No, well, you  You understand that
не Нет ну ты же понимаешь что из России
missiles will also fly from Russia when they fly. Where will
тоже полетят ракеты когда полетят Куда
they fly if something moves in our direction
полетят если если в нашу сторону что-то
in this form? Well, when look,
шевель в таком виде б Ну когда смотри
look, Ukraine is stupidly bombing Belgrade and that
смотри Украина тупо бомбит Белград и что
Russia hasn’t done anything; it’s bombing, in short,
Россия ничего не сделала бомбит короче
damn your oil refineries
блин ваши нефтеперерабатывающие заводы
Russia, that is, look We
Россия то есть смотри Мы специально
we're crossing on purpose, we're crossing more and more
переходим переходим всё больше и больше
red lines, first the Crimean Bridge we
красных линии сначала Крымский мост
looked at the reaction, no cannonballs, yes they hit
посмотрели реакцию нет ядер да ударили
Sevastopol, no cannonballs
Севастополь нет ядер
Belgorod, everyone's already used to Belgorod,
Белгород уже вс все привыкли за Белгород
even in the news for the first time, [ __ ]
уже даже в новостях первый раз бля
Belgorod, now they're all dumb and
Белгород сейчас ракетой всё немы по
hitting the Kremlin with a missile. Now everyone understands that in
Кремлю били Всё теперь все поняли что в
Russia  no eggs yes, that is, there is no
России нет яиц да то есть нету
political decision nuclear so
политического решения ядерка поэтому нет
no not Why the Russians don’t use a nuclear bomb
не Почему русские не бьют ядерной бомбы
because the Russians understand inhumane
потому что русские понима негуманно
guni prima goto Moscow nuclear
гуни примы гото Москве ядерной
bomb what will it give you Nothing absolutely Well, how
бом что это вам даст Ничего абсолютно Ну
Yes, what are the disadvantages
как Да какие минусы
Well, that’s
Ну это
good That’s not good that’s dead
хорошо Это нехорошо это очело Поче
Why why Well  You can’t think like that Why
почему Ну так нельзя мыслить Почему
so and so
такой-то
Japan signed the
Япония подписала
surrender NATO bombs on Moscow
капитуляцию натовские бом по Москве
St. Petersburg will immediately sign a capitulation with us
Питер сразу подпишет с нами капитуляцию
They will say that Moscow is illegal, look
скажут что Москва незаконно смотри
Moscow illegally moved the capital to the 17th in
Москва незаконно перенесла в 17м в 1917
1917 and the Russian Empire
году столицу да Российской империи
will proclaim a constituent assembly in St. Petersburg
провозгласят в Питере учредительное
and on its behalf they will sign the
собрание да и от его имени подпишут
capitulation and  they will say everything no we don’t want
капитуляцию и скажут всё не мы не хотим
yade we want peace am teru
яде хотим мир ам теру
dest Well, look at it, let’s do this A man is sitting
дест Ну как смотри давай так Сидит мужик
in Siberia, yes here you are in Siberia, you don’t like Moscow,
в Сибири да тут вы в Сибири Москву не
really, yes, you in Siberia don’t like Moscow and
правда да вы в Сибири Москву не любите а
Muscovites don’t like you I say, we took
москвичи вас не любят Я говорю мы делали
measurements, sociological surveys Yes  on the
замеры социологические опросы Да по
territory of the Russian Federation in the event of a
территории Российской Федерации в случае
nuclear strike on Moscow, will you be
ядерного удара по Москве будете ли вы
worried 14% 14% answered that
переживать 14% 14% ответило что будут
everyone else will just worry about
переживать остальным всем просто
Moscow, so when Moscow Everyone will just
Москву поэтому Когда Москву Все просто
sigh and go on with their
вздохнут и пойдут дальше делать свои
business And that’s it, no, no one will do that Well, so
дела И всё да нет никто так не будет Ну
what?  come on, look,
а что вот давай так вот смотри вот
look, a nuclear bomb flies across Moscow
смотри прилетает ядерная бомба по Москве
into dust and the ashes erase it. What are you doing
в пыль и прах её стирает Вы что делаете
in Siberia, we are going
в Сибири мы идём
and where you are going where you are going, who will
и куда куда идёте куда идёте кто вас
lead you there is no television in the whole village, there is
поведёт телевидения нет всё село
no Internet Where will you go? Yes, we ourselves
Интернета нет Куда вы пойдёте Да мы сами
will get there
доберёмся куда
before that  who we are and how will you
до этого до того кто нас а как вы будете
know
знать
who we will find? Well, if you can’t find
кто мы найдём Ну если вы не можете найти
where the drones
откуда беспилотники
are coming from Yes, I know everything, look No,
прилетают Да все всё знаю смотри Нет
look, I’ll say So we had
смотри я скажу Так у нас в обществе была
a discussion in society in the twenty-second year, let’s
дискуссия в двадцать втором году ээ
say about the return of nuclear weapons
скажем о возвращении ядерного оружия
specifically and so probe  and is it
специально да так зондировать и
permissible to take a
допустимо ли
preventive strike on Moscow in
превентивно по Москве в двадцать втором
2022? We took measurements:
году мы делали замеры было
14.88 about which now
14,88 про которые за сейчас
73% are for a preventive strike on
73% за удар превентивный по
Moscow. Well, you can’t hit Russia. Well,
Москве Ну нельзя бить по России Ну
why can’t you damn it, and how can we do that? It’s
почему нельзя блин а мы как тут это
not possible. It’s left in the last century
можно нельзя Это осталось в прошлом веке
now.  there are no rules anymore Russia
сейчас уже нету никаких правил Россия
is violating Russia didn’t declare war
нарушает Россия не объявляла войну
attacked us
напала на нас
So you were the first to start stirring up the first
Так вы там первый начали мутить первый
Yes and the first type of nuclear attack in Moscow Well, that’s
Да и первый типа ядерка по Москве Ну
normal And yours Why did they blow up the coca, it’s not the
норм А ваши Зачем коку подорвали не это
Tajiks, it’s a competing organization
таджики это конкурирующая организация
they, we look,
они мы смотри
we’re not Ukraine Ukraine sent after that  a
мы не Украина Украина после этого
note of protest to the government of
направила ноту протеста правительству
Tajikistan so that it looks after its
Таджикистана чтобы оно за своими
citizens and does not graze on
гражданами смотрело и не паслось на
our
нашей
territory IOC please
территории МОК пожалуста Новосибирск
give Novosibirsk to the Tajiks Yes Yekaterinburg Let
таджикам отдаём Да Екатеринбург Пусть
Moscow be the exclusive prerogative of
Москва исключительная прерогатива
Ukraine since ancient
Украины у нас издревле
times And when we see that the Tajiks are
было И когда мы смотрим что таджики
having fun there instead of us we are like this
вместо нас там отжигают мы такие это
you know it’s the same  dude, you
знаешь это всё равно что чувак ты
were growing a vegetable garden And then a dude came to dig up your
выращивал огород А тут чувак пришёл твою
potatoes and dig it up from the
картошку выкапывает это с
bottom of the crocuses from our greenhouse that they
пода крокусы с нашей оранжереи что они
came to graze there, no big deal, your submissions are
пришли пастись там нифига ваше сше
not us, look, we are not allowed in, we are
подачи не мы смотри мы не пускаем мы
against the Tajiks doing the work for us,
против того чтоб за нас работу делали
please
таджики пожалуйста
Novosibi
новосиби
Hello Yes,
Алло Да
hello again so
здравствуйте ещё
pizza salads remained
раз так пицца салаты остались
Yeah uh uh
Угу угу
uh uh
у угу
uh And what's next? Well, for example,
угу И что там дальше-то Ну например
the Chinese, we don't mind if they bang there
китайцы мы не против чтобы бахнули там
like Irkutsk, for example,
по чете Иркутску например
and the Japanese in Vladivostok Yes, the Tajiks
да японцы по Владивостоку Да таджики
Let
Пусть
uh in the center of the lupe yes and Moscow we Moscow is the
э в центре лупе да а Москву мы Москва
exclusive zone of interests of Ukraine That
исключительная зона интересов Украины То
is,  Zelensky said to us that
есть у нас Зеленский как сказал что
we must demonstratively, like
мы должны демонстративно как вот
Koshchei, he has a needle in an egg, this is death, so
Кощея у него Игла в яйце это смерть так
we must hit us like a needle with a nuclear missile, the
по мы должны как иглой ядерной ракетой
strike will be right on
ударить прямо вот удар будет прямо на
Red Square. The fact is that there are
Красную Площадь Дело в том что там есть
these surveillance cameras that are available all over
эти камеры наблюдения которые доступны
the world.  there is this moment will be
во всём мире то есть этот момент будет
recorded all over the world on
зафиксирован во всм мире на камерах
CCTV cameras and this historical
видеонаблюдения и этот исторический
moment will, as it were, solemnly go down in
момент он как бы торжественно войдёт в
history. Well, that is, we don’t feel sorry. That is,
историю Ну то есть нам не жалко То есть
in Moscow there is something like 15 million people or
в Москве Там что-то 15 млн населения или
how many in the agglomeration now I don’t know,
сколько сейчас в агломерации знаю не
I haven’t read or Ten Ten  Yes, well, they
читал или Десятка Десятка Да ну делали
simulated the strike, if one strike
моделировали удар если один удар
is done, then about a million
делается то погибнет порядка миллиона
people will die, if combined, then about 7
людей если комбинированный то порядка 7
million in the first 3
млн в первые 3
hours. Well, you know that then Ukraine is
часа Ну вы же знаете что потом Украину
just damn where did you run away,
просто блин куда ты убежал
you
вы
understand, this was the third year of
поняли шёл третий год
the special operation, the tenth year of a full-scale
спецоперации десятый год полномасштабной
war, or the eleventh already And  The Russians are
войны или одиннадцатый уже И россияне
already saying No no no no need to hit us with
уже говорят Не не не надо бить по нам
nuclear weapons no need to hit Moscow with nuclear weapons
ядерка не надо бить по Москве ядерка
subscribe to my tag right now ovin and
подпишись на мий teg прямо зараз овин а
popk more and more YouTube Zaga us
попк це дуже и дуже YouTube Зага нас
through skarg or in new ban and even more
через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
video I won’t show people immediately don’t show
вдео не показу людям вчасно не показуе
information  about streaming Tomu for this purpose
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
mi Mali operational link ppi directly
ми Мали оперативний звязок ппи прямо
infection and while there in telegra okm video
зараз а пок там в телегра окм видео ще
schezh tsikava and korisna information and we
теж цикава и корисна информация и мы
will blame you trima postiyny
повинни з вами трима постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава Украине пиши